Speaker: The Fortune Teller
PART 1
One night in London, a young police inspector called McCleary had a conversation with his wife.
ÔMy dear,Ő said McCleary. ÔI canŐt stop thinking about our neighbour, Mrs Myers.
IŐd love to know how she makes her money.
She lives so luxuriously Đ she even buys asparagus in winter!Ő
ÔLeave it to me,Ő said Mrs McCleary.
ÔI have an idea.Ő
The next day, she dressed like a young girl, took off her wedding ring and went to visit Mrs Myers.
ÔSit down, my child,Ő said Mrs Myers.
ÔWhat can I do for you?Ő
ÔIŐm going to be 20 tomorrow.
I want to know whatŐs going to happen to me in the future.Ő
Mrs Myers picked up a pack of cards and began to shuffle them.
ÔYou are MissÉ?Ő
ÔJones,Ő said Mrs McCleary, very quietly.
ÔMy dear Miss Jones,Ő said Mrs Myers.
ÔPlease take five cards and put them on the table face down.Ő